https://www.kdab.com/about/kdab-privacy-policy/

Skip to content
×
How can we help you?
Thanks for your interest in KDAB. Please write your message here and we’ll get back to you as soon as possible.
Name: *
E-Mail: *
Company:
Phone:
Message: *
I have read and agree to the terms in the Privacy Policy
Yes, sign me up for the KDAB newsletter
The information you share with us will only be used for the purpose originally intended. We will not share/pass on your information to any third parties.
×
Contact us
Germany – KDAB (Deutschland) GmbH
Reuchlinstraße 10-11, 10553 Berlin
+49 30 5213 254 70
+49 30 5213 254 99
info-de@kdab.com
Other countries
Message
Please attach your CV (PDF only)
Services
Projects
Code Migration
Modernization
Development
Consulting & Architecture
Mentoring & Support
Workshops
Why Use Qt
Automotive Suite?
Qt Automotive Suite In-depth
Training: On-Site
Qt Training
Qt Widgets for the Desktop
Qt/QML Training
Qt/QML for Embedded Training
Advanced QML Training
Advanced Qt Widgets Training
Qt Tools
Is Qt Right for Your Project?
C++
C++ Latest Standards
C++ Tools
C++ Training
Modern C++: Introduction
Modern C++: C++11 / C++14 / C++17
3D / OpenGL
OpenGL
macOS
Unix / X11 (Motif)
Resources
Blogs
KDAB TV
News
Academy
Introduction to Qt/QML
Qt Widgets and more…
Kuesa 3D
Introduction
This privacy policy sets out how KDAB uses and protects any information that you give KDAB.
KDAB is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
KDAB may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name and job title
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
your unique IP address
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
How long do we keep your information?
If you have given us your contact information so we can remain in contact you with, for example, newsletters, we will retain your information until you ask us to stop contacting you.
If you have given us your contact information so we can contact you for a quotation/proposal we may retain your information for a maximum of 3 years following contact (or sooner at your request). If we enter into any business agreements with you then we may retain your information for up to 7 years for accounting purposes.
If you have given us your personal information in relation to an employment application (CV etc.) then we will retain your personal information will be retained for a maximum of 7 years.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Our cookies are automatically set to expire after 1 year.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
You can easily delete and manage any cookies that have been installed in the cookie folder of your browser by following the instructions provided by your particular browser manufacturer.
Google Chrome
Internet Explorer
Mozilla Firefox
Safari (Desktop)
Safari (Mobile)
Android Browser
Opera
Opera Mobile
KDAB uses the AdWords and Remarketing Lists features of Google Analytics for Display Advertisers. KDAB and Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past visits to our Site. This means that vendors including Google will display KDAB promotional material on other sites you visit across the Internet.
You may opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertisers including AdWords and opt-out of customized Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Preferences Manager. To provide website visitors more choice on how their data is collected by Google Analytics, Google has developed an Opt-out Browser add-on, which is available by visiting Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on, to enable you to opt-out of Google’s programs. To opt out of the collection and use of information for ad targeting please feel free to exercise your rights, or alternatively contact KDAB.
Privacy Policy for the Use of Google Maps
This website uses Google Maps API to visually present geographical information. Google Maps is operated by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA.
When you use Google Maps, information about the use of this website, including your IP address, is transmitted to and stored on a server belonging to Google in the USA. By using this website you confirm that in this regard you are in agreement with the recording, processing and use of your automatically collected data by Google, one of its representatives, or third-party suppliers.
The terms of use for Google Maps can be found under Terms of Service for Google Maps <http://www.google.com/help/terms_maps.html>.
Full details can be found in Google’s data protection centre:
Transparency and Choice
<http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/#infochoices> and
Data Protection Policy
<http://www.google.de/policies/privacy/>.
It is possible to simply deactivate the Google Maps service and thus prevent the transfer of your data to Google by deactivating JavaScript in your browser. However, in this case you will be unable to use the map view.”
Google Web Fonts
For uniform representation of fonts, this page uses web fonts provided by Google. When you open a page, your browser loads the required web fonts into your browser cache to display texts and fonts correctly.
For this purpose your browser has to establish a direct connection to Google servers. Google thus becomes aware that our web page was accessed via your IP address. The use of Google Web fonts is done in the interest of a uniform and attractive presentation of our website. This constitutes a justified interest pursuant to Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO.
If your browser does not support web fonts, a standard font is used by your computer.
Further information about handling user data, can be found at https://developers.google.com/fonts/faq and in Google’s privacy policy at https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at info@kdab.com.
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the EU General Data Protection Regulation.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
For more information
Contact us
Improve your programming skills
Book a scheduled KDAB training!
Boost team productivity
Book an on-site training!
Access KDAB's expertise
Book a workshop!
